<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hokm Encyclopedia</string>
    <string name="home_title">Hokm Encyclopedia</string>
    <string name="home_subtitle">THE COMPLETE GUIDE TO HOKM (COURT PIECE)</string>

    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="menu_terms">Terms</string>
    <string name="menu_history">History of Hokm</string>
    <string name="menu_trivia">Hokm Trivia</string>

    <string name="about_content">This app is a lightweight offline encyclopedia for Hokm.\n\nVersion 1 focuses on fast startup, clean text pages, and simple navigation.\n\nFuture versions can add images, diagrams, and optional media.</string>
    <string name="settings_content">Settings page (starter version).\n\nIn this first release, no configurable options are enabled yet.\n\nFuture updates can include font size, dark mode, and language preferences.</string>
    <string name="rules_content">Hokm Rules (short starter text).\n\n1) Hokm is usually played by 4 players in teams of two.\n2) Each round has a trump suit chosen by the Hakem.\n3) Players must follow suit when possible.\n4) If a player cannot follow suit, they may play trump or any other card.\n5) The team that wins most tricks wins the hand.</string>
    <string name="terms_content">Hokm Terms (starter glossary).\n\nHakem: The player who chooses trump.\nTrump (Hokm): The suit that can beat cards from other suits.\nTrick: One set of four played cards, one per player.\nLead: The first card played in a trick.\nFollow suit: Playing the same suit as the lead card when possible.</string>
    <string name="history_content">History of Hokm.

Hokm is a popular trick-taking card game in Iran and neighboring regions. Its name means "trump" or "ruling suit."

The game likely evolved from older trick-taking traditions and became a social favorite because it is easy to start, strategic to master, and enjoyable in teams.

Over time, families and local groups created small rule variations, but the core idea stayed the same: choose a trump suit, win tricks, and cooperate with your partner.</string>
    <string name="trivia_content">Hokm Trivia.

• The word "Hokm" refers to the trump suit selected at the beginning of a hand.
• Team communication is indirect: players cannot reveal cards, so timing and card memory are important.
• Winning early tricks can help read opponents, but holding strong cards for later can also be decisive.
• Many players learn Hokm at home, making it both a game and a cultural tradition.</string>
    <string name="subtitle_rules">Learn the official rules of Hokm</string>
    <string name="subtitle_terms">Understand key terms and meanings</string>
    <string name="subtitle_history">Explore origins and evolution</string>
    <string name="subtitle_trivia">Test your knowledge and have fun</string>
    <string name="already_on_home">You are already on Home</string>
    <string name="coming_soon">Coming soon</string>

    <string name="about_toc">1. Purpose
2. Version focus
3. Roadmap</string>
    <string name="about_section1_title">Purpose</string>
    <string name="about_section1_body">Hokm Encyclopedia is a lightweight offline reading app focused on clear explanations about the Hokm card game.</string>
    <string name="about_section2_title">Version 1 focus</string>
    <string name="about_section2_body">This first version prioritizes readable text pages, simple navigation, and low complexity for easy updates.</string>
    <string name="about_section3_title">Roadmap</string>
    <string name="about_section3_body">Future releases can add images, examples, and optional multimedia while preserving fast startup and offline support.</string>

    <string name="settings_toc">1. Reading options
2. Navigation
3. Next additions</string>
    <string name="settings_section1_title">Reading options</string>
    <string name="settings_section1_body">This starter build keeps settings minimal to reduce complexity and maintenance overhead.</string>
    <string name="settings_section2_title">Navigation</string>
    <string name="settings_section2_body">Use the Home screen cards and footer for quick movement between key encyclopedia sections.</string>
    <string name="settings_section3_title">Next additions</string>
    <string name="settings_section3_body">Planned options include font size, dark mode, and language selection.</string>

    <string name="rules_toc">1. Players and teams
2. Trump and tricks
3. Winning a hand</string>
    <string name="rules_section1_title">Players and teams</string>
    <string name="rules_section1_body">Hokm is commonly played by four players split into two teams. Teammates sit opposite each other. The deck is shuffled and cards are dealt in batches depending on local rules. Strong partnership awareness is essential from the first trick because every card can reveal information about suit distribution.</string>
    <string name="rules_section2_title">Trump and tricks</string>
    <string name="rules_section2_body">One suit becomes trump (Hokm). Players should follow the lead suit when possible. If unable, they may play trump or any other card. Good players track which high cards have already been played, infer missing suits, and decide whether to spend or save trump for decisive moments.</string>
    <string name="rules_section3_title">Winning a hand</string>
    <string name="rules_section3_body">A team wins by taking more tricks than the opponents. Strategic timing and partnership awareness are essential. Advanced play includes sacrificing a lower-value trick to protect trump control, forcing opponents to waste trump, and creating safe leads for your partner.</string>

    <string name="terms_toc">1. Hakem
2. Trump
3. Trick and lead</string>
    <string name="terms_section1_title">Hakem</string>
    <string name="terms_section1_body">Hakem is the player who chooses the trump suit at the beginning of the hand.</string>
    <string name="terms_section2_title">Trump (Hokm)</string>
    <string name="terms_section2_body">Trump is the ruling suit that can beat cards from other suits when played on a trick. Managing trump means balancing offense and defense: using trump aggressively to capture key tricks, or conserving trump to stop opponent runs later in the hand.</string>
    <string name="terms_section3_title">Trick and lead</string>
    <string name="terms_section3_body">A trick is one round of four played cards. The lead is the first card in that trick.</string>

    <string name="history_toc">1. Origins
2. Popularity
3. Local variations</string>
    <string name="history_section1_title">Origins</string>
    <string name="history_section1_body">Hokm developed from classic trick-taking traditions and became widespread in Iran and nearby regions.</string>
    <string name="history_section2_title">Popularity</string>
    <string name="history_section2_body">Its popularity comes from simple rules, strong strategy depth, and social team-based play. Hokm is often taught informally at home, where people learn practical tactics—counting cards, reading patterns, and coordinating silently with a partner.</string>
    <string name="history_section3_title">Local variations</string>
    <string name="history_section3_body">Families and communities often adopt minor rule variations, while the core trump-and-trick structure remains the same.</string>

    <string name="trivia_toc">1. Name meaning
2. Strategy insight
3. Cultural note</string>
    <string name="trivia_section1_title">Name meaning</string>
    <string name="trivia_section1_body">The word "Hokm" refers to the trump suit, the suit that has special power in each hand.</string>
    <string name="trivia_section2_title">Strategy insight</string>
    <string name="trivia_section2_body">Top players balance short-term trick wins with long-term control of trump cards and information. They observe small signals such as hesitation, repeated suit leads, and card tempo to estimate likely holdings.</string>
    <string name="trivia_section3_title">Cultural note</string>
    <string name="trivia_section3_body">For many people, Hokm is both a game and a shared tradition played across generations.</string>

    <string name="about_note">Important: This page provides a quick orientation before you dive into detailed sections.</string>
    <string name="settings_note">Tip: Keep defaults for a clean reading experience; customization can come later.</string>
    <string name="rules_note">Important: Following suit when possible is one of the key principles in Hokm.</string>
    <string name="terms_note">Tip: Learning these core terms first will make advanced rules much easier to understand.</string>
    <string name="history_note">Did you know? Hokm has remained popular largely because of its team strategy depth.</string>
    <string name="trivia_note">Fun fact: Even experienced players discover new tactical patterns over time.</string>
</resources>
